Wauregan and Quinebaug Company Records 1981.0010
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series VI: Labor Records, 1855-1958
  - Subseries C: Personnel Files, 1936-1958
    - Beauregard, Rita, L. G., 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1210)
    - Beauregard, Rose L., 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1211)
    - Beausoleil, Albina, 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1212)
    - Beausoleil, Beatrice, 1951 (Box 209, Folder 1213)
    - Beausoleil, Calixte, 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1214)
    - Beausoleil, Dorilla V., 1943 (Box 209, Folder 1215)
    - Beausoleil, Henry, 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1216)
    - Beausoleil, Henry Robert, 1947 (Box 209, Folder 1217)
    - Beausoleil, Jeannette, 1953 (Box 209, Folder 1218)
    - Beausoleil, Lorraine, 1948 (Box 209, Folder 1219)
    - Beausoleil, Marielle, 1956 (Box 209, Folder 1220)
    - Beausoleil, Roger J., 1948 (Box 209, Folder 1221)
    - Beausoliel, Antonio, 1956 (Box 209, Folder 1222)
    - Beauvais, Edgar R., 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1223)
    - Beauvais, Nellie L., 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1224)
    - Bebo, Arthur A., 1952 (Box 209, Folder 1225)
    - Bedard, Alfred, 1950 (Box 209, Folder 1226)
    - Bedard, Delphis, 1950 (Box 209, Folder 1227)
    - Bedard, Joseph, 1949 (Box 209, Folder 1228)
    - Bedard, Lillian, 1956 (Box 209, Folder 1229)
    - Bedard, Lydia, 1957 (Box 209, Folder 1230)
    - Bedard, Norman, 1953 (Box 209, Folder 1231)
    - Bedard, Oscar, 1943 (Box 209, Folder 1232)
    - Bedard, Roland, 1952 (Box 209, Folder 1233)
    - Bednarz, Ignatius, 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1234)
    - Belanger, Adrien L. P., 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1235)
    - Belanger, Gerard, 1955 (Box 206, Folder 1236)
    - Belanger, Gertrude B. Poirier, 1944 (Box 209, Folder 1237)
    - Belanger, Rosalie A., 1937 (Box 209, Folder 1238)
    - Belanger, Rose H., 1937 (Box 209, Folder 1239)
    - Belanger, Sidney, 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1240)
    - Belanger, Theodore Alfred, 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1241)
    - Belanger, Vivian I., 1944 (Box 209, Folder 1242)
    - Belisle, Arthur, 1955 (Box 209, Folder 1243)
    - Belisle, Charles H., 1954 (Box 209, Folder 1244)
    - Belisle, Ernest, 1950 (Box 209, Folder 1245)
    - Belisle, Ernest, 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1246)
    - Belisle, George E., Sr., 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1247)
    - Belisle, George H., Jr., 1940 (Box 209, Folder 1248)
    - Belisle, Laura, 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1249)
    - Belisle, Liza, 1956 (Box 209, Folder 1250)
    - Bellanceau, Eugene, 1953 (Box 209, Folder 1251)
    - Bellanceau, Helen L., 1951 (Box 209, Folder 1252)
    - Bellavance, Gerald E., 1953 (Box 209, Folder 1253)
    - Bellavance, Julia, 1957 (Box 209, Folder 1254)
    - Bellavance, Mary E. P., 1940 (Box 209, Folder 1255)
    - Bellevance, Andrew, 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1256)
    - Bellisario, Henry J., 1943 (Box 209, Folder 1257)
    - Belson, Etoila A., 1953 (Box 209, Folder 1258)
    - Belval, Alvin, 1955 (Box 209, Folder 1259)
    - Belval, Arthur E., 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1260)
    - Belval, Damase, 1950 (Box 209, Folder 1261)
    - Belval, Lydia B., 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1262)
    - Belval, Peter S., 1940 (Box 209, Folder 1263)
    - Benac, Robert W., 1946 (Box 209, Folder 1264)
    - Bennett, Alice, 1945 (Box 209, Folder 1265)
    - Bennett, Fred, 1953 (Box 209, Folder 1266)
    - Bennett, Fred, 1953 (Box 209, Folder 1267)
    - Bennett, Lester, 1952 (Box 209, Folder 1268)
    - Bennett, Marjorie, 1952 (Box 209, Folder 1269)
    - Bennett, Mary I., 1943 (Box 209, Folder 1270)
    - Benoit, Albert A., 1957 (Box 209, Folder 1271)
    - Benoit, Alexander, 1957 (Box 209, Folder 1272)
    - Benoit, Arthur J., 191955 (Box 209, Folder 1273)
    - Benoit, Claire G., 1945 (Box 209, Folder 1274)
    - Benoit, Frederick, 1950 (Box 209, Folder 1275)
    - Benoit, Helen, 1952 (Box 209, Folder 1276)
    - Benoit, Joseph, 1945 (Box 209, Folder 1277)
    - Benoit, Joseph E., 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1278)
    - Benoit, Laura M. P., 1956 (Box 209, Folder 1279)
    - Benoit, Leo A., 1949 (Box 209, Folder 1280)
    - Benoit, Mary A., 1956 (Box 209, Folder 1281)
    - Benoit, Rene C., 1947 (Box 209, Folder 1282)
    - Benoit, Roland, 1955 (Box 209, Folder 1283)
    - Benoit, Virginia L., 1947 (Box 209, Folder 1284)
    - Benoit, William J., 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1285)
    - Benton, Dora, 1943 (Box 209, Folder 1286)
    - Benway, Gladys, 1937 (Box 209, Folder 1287)
    - Benway, Lee W., 1951 (Box 209, Folder 1288)
    - Benway, Mary L., 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1289)
    - Benway, Paul, 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1290)
    - Berger, Blanche Y. Menard, 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1291)
    - Berger, Thomas, 1956 (Box 209, Folder 1292)
    - Bergeron, Edward J., 1940 (Box 209, Folder 1293)
    - Bergeron, Fabien, 1938 (Box 209, Folder 1294)
    - Bergeron, Fortuna, 1940 (Box 209, Folder 1295)
    - Bergeron, Loretta M. D., 1940 (Box 209, Folder 1296)
    - Bergeron, Marguerite, 1954 (Box 209, Folder 1297)
    - Bergeron, Ovide T., 1955 (Box 209, Folder 1298)
    - Bergeron, Robert F., 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1299)
    - Bergman, Vivian, 1948 (Box 209, Folder 1300)
    - Berkowitz, Henry, 1956 (Box 209, Folder 1301)
    - Bernard, Alfred, 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1302)
    - Bernard, Aurelie B., 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1303)
    - Bernard, Marie B., 1937 (Box 209, Folder 1304)
    - Bernat, Emma R., 1954 (Box 209, Folder 1305)
    - Bernat, Madeline P., 1954 (Box 209, Folder 1306)
    - Bernier, Adrien, 1956 (Box 209, Folder 1307)
    - Bernier, Agnes, 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1308)
    - Bernier, Anselm, 1956 (Box 209, Folder 1309)
    - Bernier, Antonio, 1953 (Box 209, Folder 1310)
    - Bernier, Armand A., 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1311)
    - Bernier, Bertha, 1939 (Box 209, Folder 1312)
    - Bernier, Blanche G., 1937 (Box 209, Folder 1313)
    - Bernier, Blandine M. A. C., 1938 (Box 209, Folder 1314)
    - Bernier, Celina C., 1937 (Box 209, Folder 1315)
    - Bernier, Claire V., 1940 (Box 209, Folder 1316)
    - Bernier, Clarinda, 1953 (Box 209, Folder 1317)
    - Bernier, Conrad, 1942 (Box 209, Folder 1318)
    - Bernier, Delina B., 1947 (Box 209, Folder 1319)
    - Bernier, Edgar, 1949 (Box 209, Folder 1320)
    - Bernier, Etiennette, 1948 (Box 210, Folder 1321)
    - Bernier, Eugene, 1938 (Box 210, Folder 1322)
    - Bernier, Eva D., 1945 (Box 210, Folder 1320)
    - Bernier, Florence, 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1324)
    - Bernier, Genevieve F., 1952 (Box 210, Folder 1325)
    - Bernier, Gerard G., 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1326)
    - Bernier, Gertrude, 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1327)
    - Bernier, Gracia G., 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1328)
    - Bernier, Henrietta, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1329)
    - Bernier, Henry, 1948 (Box 210, Folder 1330)
    - Bernier, Irene B., 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1331)
    - Bernier, Irene McMahon, 1945 (Box 210, Folder 1332)
    - Bernier, John, 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1333)
    - Bernier, Joseph, 1945 (Box 210, Folder 1334)
    - Bernier, Joseph A., 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1335)
    - Bernier, Harry, 1951 (Box 210, Folder 1336)
    - Bernier, Laurence, 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1337)
    - Bernier, Leodore H., 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1338)
    - Bernier, Leopold, 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1339)
    - Bernier, Mary Jane R. A., 1938 (Box 210, Folder 1340)
    - Bernier, Mina R., 1945 (Box 210, Folder 1341)
    - Bernier, Napoleon, 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1342)
    - Bernier, Omer, 1951 (Box 210, Folder 1343)
    - Bernier, Rebecca G., 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1344)
    - Bernier, Rita, 1954 (Box 210, Folder 1345)
    - Bernier, Samuel J., 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1346)
    - Bernier, Urbain J., 1938 (Box 210, Folder 1347)
    - Bernier, William, 1938 (Box 210, Folder 1348)
    - Bernier, Yvonne, 1945 (Box 210, Folder 1349)
    - Berns, Jerry, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1350)
    - Berris, Dionysios, 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1351)
    - Bertrand, Raymond, 1939 (Box 210, Folder 1352)
    - Berube, Albert, 1950 (Box 210, Folder 1353)
    - Berube, Edgar E., Jr., 1955 (Box 210, Folder 1354)
    - Berube, Edgar J., 1954 (Box 210, Folder 1355)
    - Berube, Ernest J., 1952 (Box 210, Folder 1356)
    - Berube, Joseph Henry, 1947 (Box 210, Folder 1357)
    - Bersani, Florence E., 1951 (Box 210, Folder 1358)
    - Bessette, Anna, 1946 (Box 210, Folder 1359)
    - Bessette, Emery J., 1950 (Box 210, Folder 1360)
    - Bessette, Ernest, Sr., 1954 (Box 210, Folder 1361)
    - Bessette, Ernest G., Jr., 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1362)
    - Bessette, Ernest Joseph, 1945 (Box 210, Folder 1363)
    - Bessette, Fred, 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1364)
    - Bessette, Lillian M., 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1365)
    - Bessette, Orianna Dore, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1366)
    - Bessette, Raymond E., 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1367)
    - Bessette, Yvonne L., 1939 (Box 210, Folder 1368)
    - Bibeault, Albert, 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1369)
    - Bibeault, Alferie J., 1939 (Box 210, Folder 1370)
    - Bibeault, Eleanor C., 1947 (Box 210, Folder 1371)
    - Bill, Earl, 1954 (Box 210, Folder 1372)
    - Bill, Jeanne Gladu, 1957 (Box 210, Folder 1373)
    - Billings, Wilfred, 1952 (Box 210, Folder 1374)
    - Billings, Yvonne, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1375)
    - Billington, Byron A., 1957 (Box 210, Folder 1376)
    - Billington, Chester V., 1950 (Box 210, Folder 1377)
    - Billington, Edmond, 1948 (Box 210, Folder 1378)
    - Billington, Eleanor T., 1952 (Box 210, Folder 1379)
    - Bilodeau, Leo, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1380)
    - Bishop, Joseph L., 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1381)
    - Bishop, Rosanna Dion, 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1382)
    - Bisson, Lillian, 1951 (Box 210, Folder 1383)
    - Bisson, Norman, 1944 (Box 210, Folder 1384)
    - Bissonnette, Adelard, 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1385)
    - Bissonnette, Bernadette, 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1386)
    - Bissonnette, Camil, 1948 (Box 210, Folder 1387)
    - Bissonnette, Docina T., 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1388)
    - Bissonnette, George D., 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1389)
    - Bissonnette, Juliette Rita, 1951 (Box 210, Folder 1390)
    - Bissonnette, Mary Louise, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1391)
    - Bissonnette, Rodney, 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1392)
    - Bissonnette, Theresa, 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1393)
    - Bissonnette, Victor, 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1394)
    - Bissonnette, William, 1957 (Box 210, Folder 1395)
    - Bizaillon, Rita B., 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1396)
    - Bjork, Helga, 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1397)
    - Black, Agnes, 1950 (Box 210, Folder 1398)
    - Blain, Fernand, 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1399)
    - Blain, Loretta, 1949 (Box 210, Folder 1400)
    - Blain, Lucien F., 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1401)
    - Blain, Wilfred H., 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1402)
    - Blair, Virgil P., 1947 (Box 210, Folder 1403)
    - Blais, Aldage, 1950 (Box 210, Folder 1404)
    - Blais, Donat, 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1405)
    - Blais, Eugene, 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1406)
    - Blais, Francois X., 1952 (Box 210, Folder 1407)
    - Blais, Frank, 1946 (Box 210, Folder 1408)
    - Blais, Gerard J., 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1409)
    - Blais, Grace F., 1939 (Box 210, Folder 1410)
    - Blais, Lorique, 1956 (Box 210, Frame 1411)
    - Blais, Marie A. A., 1939 (Box 210, Folder 1412)
    - Blais, Marie P. R., 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1413)
    - Blais, Neil R., 1954 (Box 210, Folder 1414)
    - Blais, Rose, Z. B., 1950 (Box 210, Folder 1415)
    - Blake, Myrtice, 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1416)
    - Blakeley, William E., 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1417)
    - Blanchard, Emma B., 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1418)
    - Blanchard, Lionel, 1954 (Box 210, Folder 1419)
    - Blanchette, Blanche V., 1957 (Box 210, Folder 1420)
    - Blanchette, Eusebe, 1938 (Box 210, Folder 1421)
    - Blanchette, Floreina, 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1422)
    - Blanchette, Harvey, 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1423)
    - Blanchette, Irene Couture, 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1424)
    - Blanchette, Maria, 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1425)
    - Blanchette, Napoleon, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1426)
    - Blanchette, Peter A., 1950 (Box 210, Folder 1427)
    - Blanchette, Raymond, 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1428)
    - Blanchette, Sarah, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1429)
    - Blanchette, Viola B., 1948 (Box 210, Folder 1430)
    - Blank, Majer, 1957 (Box 210, Folder 1431)
    - Blankenship, Sterling, 1950 (Box 210, Folder 1432)
    - Blezard, Ernest, 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1433)
    - Bobinski, Annie R., 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1434)
    - Bobinski, Michael, 1944 (Box 210, Folder 1435)
    - Bobinski, Stanley J., 1938 (Box 210, Folder 1436)
    - Bodeau, Celena, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1437)
    - Bodo, Eva L., 1949 (Box 210, Folder 1438)
    - Bodo, George J., 1938 (Box 210, Folder 1439)
    - Bogdon, Adol, 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1440)
    - Bohara, Agnes, 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1441)
    - Boilard, Gerard, 1954 (Box 210, Folder 1442)
    - Boisclair, Orina, 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1443)
    - Boiselle, Albert, 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1444)
    - Boivin, Albina M. R., 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1445)
    - Boivin, Gerard, 1952 (Box 210, Folder 1446)
    - Boivin, Irene B., 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1447)
    - Bolduc, Adelard, 1945 (Box 210, Folder 1448)
    - Bolduc, Robert T., 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1449)
    - Bolduc, Urbain, 1952 (Box 210, Folder 1450)
    - Bolton, Frederick A., 1938 (Box 210, Folder 1451)
    - Bonczek, Sigmund M., 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1452)
    - Bondulich, Roy M., 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1453)
    - Bonin, Dorothy, 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1454)
    - Bonneau, Antonia V. T., 1939 (Box 210, Folder 1455)
    - Bonneau, Gertrude S., 1938 (Box 210, Folder 1456)
    - Bonneau, Henry, 1945 (Box 210, Folder 1457)
    - Bonneau, Julia, 1945 (Box 210, Folder 1458)
    - Bonneau, Lorraine, 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1459)
    - Bonneau, Louise, 1945 (Box 210, Folder 1460)
    - Bonneau, Lucille T. Corbeil, 1946 (Box 210, Folder 1461)
    - Bonneau, Ovila, 1947 (Box 210, Folder 1462)
    - Bonneau, Philip I., 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1463)
    - Bonneau, Raoul J., 1955 (Box 210, Folder 1464)
    - Bonneau, Trettle J., 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1465)
    - Bonneau, Yvonne, 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1466)
    - Bonnin, Annette D., 1946 (Box 210, Folder 1467)
    - Bonnin, Brida A., 1944 (Box 210, Folder 1468)
    - Bonnin, Henry, 1950 (Box 210, Folder 1469)
    - Bonnin, Joseph C., 1942 (Box 210, Folder 1470)
    - Bonnin, Oliver, 1951 (Box 210, Folder 1471)
    - Booth, Harry A., 1957 (Box 210, Folder 1472)
    - Borodezt, William, 1955 (Box 210, Folder 1473)
    - Boroski, Mamie R., 1946 (Box 210, Folder 1474)
    - Borse, John, Jr., 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1475)
    - Boskovitch, Thomas, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1476)
    - Bouchard, Agnes C., 1947 (Box 210, Folder 1477)
    - Bouchard, Albert A., Jr., 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1478)
    - Bouchard, Arthur, 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1479)
    - Bouchard, Doris B., 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1480)
    - Bouchard, Gerald A., 1939 (Box 210, Folder 1481)
    - Bouchard, Joseph P. F., 1957 (Box 210, Folder 1482)
    - Bouchard, Lena, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1483)
    - Bouchard, Philippe, 1939 (Box 210, Folder 1484)
    - Bouchard, Raymond L., 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1485)
    - Bouchard, Raymond W., 1951 (Box 210, Folder 1486)
    - Bouchard, William, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1487)
    - Bouchard, Mary O. C., 1956 (Box 210, Folder 1488)
    - Boucher, Agnes M. B., 1954 (Box 210, Folder 1489)
    - Boucher, Rose L. B., 1952 (Box 210, Folder 1490)
    - Boucher, Aldemore, 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1491)
    - Boucher, Arthur L., 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1492)
    - Boucher, Eli, 1957 (Box 210, Folder 1493)
    - Boucher, Elzear, 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1494)
    - Boucher, John A., 1953 (Box 210, Folder 1495)
    - Boucher, Joseph, 1939 (Box 210, Folder 1496)
    - Boucher, Julien L., 1957 (Box 210, Folder 1497)
    - Boucher, Mary L. D. P., 1938 (Box 210, Folder 1498)
    - Boucher, Peter, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 1499)
    - Boucher, Regina C., 1940 (Box 210, Folder 1500)
    - Boucher, Rosario, 1937 (Box 210, Folder 1501)
    - Boucher, Sara G., 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1502)
    - Bougie, Theresa, 1952 (Box 211, Folder 1503)
    - Boulais, Cecile, 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1504)
    - Boulais, George A., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1505)
    - Boulais, Grace, 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1506)
    - Boulais, Madeline L., 1940 (Box 211, Folder 1507)
    - Boulay, Laurianne, 1954 (Box 229, Folder 5133)
    - Boulay, Laurianne, 1954 (Box 211, Folder 1508)
    - Boulay, Maurice J., 1939 (Box 211, Folder 1509)
    - Bourassa, Elodia B., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1510)
    - Bourassa, Lucien, 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1511)
    - Bourbeau, Dorothy, 1946 (Box 211, Folder 1512)
    - Bourbeau, Ernest A., 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1513)
    - Bourey, Blanche B., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1514)
    - Bourey, Eugene S., 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1515)
    - Bourey, Joseph W., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1516)
    - Bourey, Theresa, 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1517)
    - Bourque, Amelia P., 1940 (Box 211, Folder 1518)
    - Bourque, Arthur A., 1952 (Box 211, Folder 1519)
    - Bourque, Charles A., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1520)
    - Bourque, Dewey P., 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1521)
    - Bourque, Eugene, 1951 (Box 211, Folder 1522)
    - Bourque, Gladys D., 1939 (Box 211, Folder 1523)
    - Bourque, Irene, 1957 (Box 211, Folder 1524)
    - Bourque, John B., 1938 (Box 211, Folder 1525)
    - Bourque, Loretta, 1957 (Box 211, Frame 1526)
    - Bourque, Lucien, 1951 (Box 211, Folder 1527)
    - Bourque, Lucille, 1946 (Box 211, Folder 1528)
    - Bourque, Yvonne D. M., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1529)
    - Bousquet, Adrienne X., 1939 (Box 211, Folder 1530)
    - Bousquet, Amelia C., 1944 (Box 211, Folder 1531)
    - Bousquet, Barbara, 1957 (Box 211, Folder 1532)
    - Bousquet, Bernadette R., 1947 (Box 211, Folder 1533)
    - Bousquet, Ernest L., 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1534)
    - Bousquet, Fabiola A., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1535)
    - Bousquet, Francis, 1955 (Box 211, Folder 1536)
    - Bousquet, George, 1944 (Box 211, Folder 1537)
    - Bousquet, Gerard J., 1952 (Box 211, Folder 1538)
    - BOusquet, Joseph L., 1938 (Box 211, Folder 1539)
    - Bousquet, Laurence J., 1940 (Box 211, Folder 1540)
    - Bousquet, Nelson, 1948 (Box 211, Folder 1541)
    - Bousquet, Rosario A., 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1542)
    - Bousquet, Vivian, 1955 (Box 211, Folder 1543)
    - Bouthillier, Achille F., 1950 (Box 211, Folder 1544)
    - Bouthillier, Adrian L., 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1545)
    - Bouthillier, Armand, 1950 (Box 211, Folder 1546)
    - Bouthillier, Eva R. G., 1938 (Box 211, Folder 1547)
    - Bouthillier, Mildred L. T., 1954 (Box 211, Folder 1548)
    - Boutin, Odilon, 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1549)
    - Boutin, Robert, 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1550)
    - Boutin, Urbain E., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1551)
    - Bowen, Harold, 1949 (Box 211, Folder 1552)
    - Bowden, Harvey, 1955 (Box 211, Folder 1553)
    - Bowers, Eugene, 1951 (Box 211, Folder 1554)
    - Bowers, Lydia, 1955 (Box 211, Folder 1555)
    - Bradley, Arlene R., 1939 (Box 211, Folder 1556)
    - Braley, Charles W., 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1557)
    - Braley, Warren C., 1952 (Box 211, Folder 1558)
    - Bransfield, Lea D., 1939 (Box 211, Folder 1559)
    - Brault, Romeo H., 1940 (Box 211, Folder 1560)
    - Breault, Angela, 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1561)
    - Breault, Angelle, 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1562)
    - Breault, Blanche, 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1563)
    - Breault, Medee J., 1939 (Box 211, Folder 1564)
    - Brenek, Doris, 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1565)
    - Brennan, Nora R., 1951 (Box 211, Folder 1566)
    - Bressette, John, 1943 (Box 211, Folder 1567)
    - Bressette, Lillian, 1944 (Box 211, Folder 1568)
    - Breton, Adelard J., 1939 (Box 211, Folder 1569)
    - Breton, Emma, 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1570)
    - Breton, Norman, 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1571)
    - Breton, Raymond, 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1572)
    - Breton, Rose A., 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1573)
    - Briere, Albert L., 1950 (Box 211, Folder 1574)
    - Briere, Blanche P., 1952 (Box 211, Folder 1575)
    - Briere, Hosea, 1952 (Box 211, Folder 1576)
    - Briere, John L., 1951 (Box 211, Folder 1577)
    - Briere, Joseph L., 1947 (Box 211, Folder 1578)
    - Briere, Maurice, 1952 (Box 211, Folder 1579)
    - Briere, Norman A., 1950 (Box 211, Folder 1580)
    - Briere, Osea J., 1955 (Box 211, Folder 1581)
    - Briere, Peter, 1955 (Box 211, Folder 1582)
    - Briere, Rita J., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1583)
    - Briere, Yvonne M., 1957 (Box 211, Folder 1584)
    - Briquier, Blanche H., 1954 (Box 211, Folder 1585)
    - Briquier, Edward, 1943 (Box 211, Folder 1586)
    - Brisson, Abbie Visenalda, 1945 (Box 211, Folder 1587)
    - Brisson, Florence, 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1588)
    - Brisson, Francis Leonel, 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1589)
    - Brisson, Pauline Plantier, 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1590)
    - Broadhurst, Josephine P., 1950 (Box 211, Folder 1591)
    - Brodeur, Alphonse, 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1592)
    - Brodeur, Arthur, 1949 (Box 211, Folder 1593)
    - Brodeur, Aurora B., 1944 (Box 211, Folder 1594)
    - Brodeur, Benjamin A., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1595)
    - Brodeur, Charles, 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1596)
    - Brodeur, Charles E., 1946 (Box 211, Folder 1597)
    - Brodeur, Donat Harvey, 1948 (Box 211, Folder 1598)
    - Brodeur, Eileen M., 1945 (Box 211, Folder 1599)
    - Brodeur, Elise, 1949 (Box 211, Folder 1600)
    - Brodeur, George J., 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1601)
    - Brodeur, Gerard, 1949 (Box 211, Folder 1602)
    - Brodeur, Helen P. Courcy, 1947 (Box 211, Folder 1603)
    - Brodeur, Henry, 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1604)
    - Brodeur, Jeanine C., 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1605)
    - Brodeur, Laurent, 1950 (Box 211, Folder 1606)
    - Brodeur, Lauretta T., 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1607)
    - Brodeur, Lillian E. Lacroix, 1957 (Box 211, Folder 1608)
    - Brodeur, Lionel L., 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1609)
    - Brodeur, Louis A., 1940 (Box 211, Folder 1610)
    - Brodeur, Lucien J., 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1611)
    - Brodeur, Montcalm J., 1950 (Box 211, Folder 1612)
    - Brodeur, Odna C., 1939 (Box 211, Folder 1613)
    - Brodeur, Rose A. D., 1940 (Box 211, Folder 1614)
    - Brodeur, Rose G., 1944 (Box 211, Folder 1615)
    - Brodeur, Staneslos, 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1616)
    - Brodeur, Theresa, 1948 (Box 211, Folder 1617)
    - Brodeur, Viola P. Kerr, 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1618)
    - Bromley, Richard, 1950 (Box 211, Folder 1619)
    - Bromley, Robert A., 1946 (Box 211, Folder 1620)
    - Brosseau, Lionel, 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1621)
    - Brouillard, Adeline B., 1940 (Box 211, Folder 1622)
    - Brouillard, Armand J., 1950 (Box 211, Folder 1623)
    - Brouillard, Joseph, 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1624)
    - Brouillard, Malvina St.P., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1625)
    - Brouillard, Marie I. D., 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1626)
    - Brouillard, Odelan J., 1940 (Box 211, Folder 1627)
    - Brouillard, Ovila J., 1939 (Box 211, Folder 1628)
    - Brouillard, Rhea A., 1944 (Box 211, Folder 1629)
    - Brouillard, Ronald, 1944 (Box 211, Folder 1630)
    - Brousseau, Adelard J., Jr., 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1631)
    - Brown, Ann H., 1937 (Box 211, Folder 1632)
    - Brown, Ellen C., 1943 (Box 211, Folder 1633)
    - Brown, George, 1946 (Box 211, Folder 1634)
    - Brown, Gertrude, 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1635)
    - Brown, John W., 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1636)
    - Brown, Mathilda B., 1946 (Box 211, Folder 1637)
    - Brown, Percy, Jr., 1951 (Box 211, Folder 1638)
    - Brown, Raymond, Jr., 1955 (Box 211, Folder 1639)
    - Brown, Remelia Aubin, 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1640)
    - Bruce, Jack D., 1946 (Box 211, Folder 1641)
    - Bruels, Cecile J., 1954 (Box 211, Folder 1642)
    - Bruley, Mitchell, 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1643)
    - Brumble, Teresa, 1951 (Box 211, Folder 1644)
    - Brunell, Alfred, 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1645)
    - Brunelle, Gerard, 1956 (Box 211, Folder 1646)
    - Brunet, David N., 1950 (Box 211, Folder 1647)
    - Brunet, Ephrem J., 1953 (Box 211, Folder 1648)
    - Brunet, Gerard, 1940 (Box 211, Folder 1649)
    - Brunet, Lucien J., 1940 (Box 211, Folder 1650)
    - Brunet, Mary A., 1947 (Box 211, Folder 1651)
    - Buckwold, Donald E., 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1652)
    - Buczak, Adam, 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1653)